Catoya L. Lundy

1166 Fulton Street, Brooklyn, NY 11216

Phone: (860) 965-2194

Email: catova.lundy@hotmail.com

Employment Objective

The ability to apply my exceptional organizational skills, extensive knowledge, and years of 11 years experience as an legal secretary/assistant for an organization that offers a challenge, opportunity for personal growth, and new learning experiences.

Qualifications

- Typing skills average 80-90 wpm
- a polite and courteous disposition;
- · exceptional organizational skills;
- punctual; ability to work in fast paced, high pressure situations.
- Proficient in the following software/systems: NEEDLES, MAC OS, Microsoft Office (Word, Outlook, Excel, PowerPoint), Lotus Notes, Adobe Acrobat Professional, Docs Open, Desksite, Accuroute, Deltaview, Styles, MacPac and the Internet.

Education and Training

B.A. in Liberal Studies, Saint Joseph College, West Hartford, Connecticut New York University, New York, New York

2002 - 2006

1996

Employment History

Weil, Gotshal & Manges, New York, NY Corporate Legal Assistant –Partner

July 2007 -present

Full-time Legal secretary to corporate partner and three associate attorneys. Duties include but are not limited to phone reception, copying, faxing, scanning, opening new client matters, calendar management, file organization, drafting of correspondence, document revisions and proofreading, client billing, expense reimbursements, travel arrangements, conference room reservations, ordering of supplies and attorney time entries. Overtime coordinator for the 28th and 30th Floors.

Willcutts Law Group, Hartford, CT

June 2006 - July 2007

Legal Secretary

Full-time legal secretary to partner and one associate. Heavy phone reception; calendar management; dictation; requesting medical records, bills, and lost wage information; drafting pleadings and discovery documentation including filing appearances, drafting motions, writ summons and complaints, interrogatories and request for production, deposition notices, and subpoenas; drafting and filing of worker's compensation forms and appearances; file organization and management; correspondence and contact with clients, insurance companies, courts, police departments, marshals, and attorneys; filing; client related expense accounting;

Law Office of Kenneth P. Namnoum, Hartford, CT

Oct 2006 - Nov 2006

Legal Secretary

Part-time/temporary legal secretary position phone reception, drafting of pleadings and discovery documentation, file organization, and correspondence with clients and medical provider

Law Office of Steven F. Meo, Hartford, CT

October 1999 - March 2006

Legal Secretary/Office Manager

Full-time Office Manager/Paralegal/Legal Secretary to firm owner and associate. Heavy phone reception; calendar management; dictation; requesting medical records, bills, and lost wage information; drafting pleadings and discovery documentation including filing appearances, drafting motions, writ summons and complaints, interrogatories and request for production, deposition notices, and subpoenas; drafting and filing of worker's compensation forms and appearances; file organization and management; correspondence and contact with clients, insurance companies, courts, police departments, marshals, and attorneys; filing; client related expense accounting; billing, ordering and maintenance of office supplies.

Personal Information

NY Cares Volunteer.

References

David M. Poirot, Esq. Gold & Levy 21 Oak Street, Suite 300 Hartford, CT 06106 Phone: (860) 549-5152

Suzanne Lee Weil, Gotshal & Manges 767 Fifth Avenue New York, NY 10153 Phone: (212) 310-8154